Register of the Socialist Workers Party Records, 1928-1990
Hoover Institution Archives
- AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL, 1937-1978. (Box No. 103)
  - Phonotape cassettes from Gelfand vs. Smith et al. trial
    - Exhibit no. 19 (Alan Gelfand-Peter Camejo conversation, 1978) (Folder 12)